{"data": [{"id": 0, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Remains at Red Cedar River?", "answer": "[crazy new website called Google](https://www.google.com/search?q=is+spreading+ashes+illegal&oq=is+spreading+ash&gs_lcrp=EgZjaHJvbWUqBwgBEAAYgAQyBggAEEUYOTIHCAEQABiABDIHCAIQABiABDIHCAMQABiABDIHCAQQABiABDIHCAUQABiABDIICAYQABgWGB4yCAgHEAAYFhgeMggICBAAGBYYHjIICAkQABgWGB7SAQg1ODg5ajBqN6gCALACAA&sourceid=chrome&ie=UTF-8)"}, {"id": 1, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Is there any electrical engineering alumni in MSU give suggestions on EE internship on Michigan??", "answer": "Graduated with an EE degree last May. Internships my Freshman year were difficult due to Covid. Sophomore year, I went to the career fair (was virtual) and scheduled as many one-on-ones as I could. I had a couple of different offers but went with the one that worked best for me. Always go to the Fall career fair, because you have the highest chance of landing an internship/job (not always the case but was for me)."}, {"id": 2, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Is there any electrical engineering alumni in MSU give suggestions on EE internship on Michigan??", "answer": "LinkedIn is your friend! Also hit up an advisor, they might have some leads"}, {"id": 3, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Is there any electrical engineering alumni in MSU give suggestions on EE internship on Michigan??", "answer": "Recent graduate here, what I did to help get myself internship opportunities was to get as much experience as possible. There are plenty of design clubs/teams and research you can get involved with on campus. Depending on what you join, you could possibly have recruiters reaching out to you."}, {"id": 4, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Is there any electrical engineering alumni in MSU give suggestions on EE internship on Michigan??", "answer": "Use your connections.  It\u2019s how I\u2019ve gotten almost every job.  Just ask around if you know of anyone within the EE industry."}, {"id": 5, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Will I get in??", "answer": "you\u2019ll probably get waitlisted, if you do send in a letter of continued interest it\u2019ll help your chances of"}, {"id": 6, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that INSANE STAT: The 2000 National Championship MSU team played 5 games that season against teams that made the Final Four and went 5-0?", "answer": "Wisconsin 4 times, and Florida once. Good attempt at twisting yesterday's big reveal about Wisconsin 4 times."}, {"id": 7, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that INSANE STAT: The 2000 National Championship MSU team played 5 games that season against teams that made the Final Four and went 5-0?", "answer": "They also beat North Carolina that year in Chapel Hill"}, {"id": 8, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that INSANE STAT: The 2000 National Championship MSU team played 5 games that season against teams that made the Final Four and went 5-0?", "answer": "I was a student at this time and it was a wild ride. Beating a very good Wisconsin team that many times in a season was crazy."}, {"id": 9, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that INSANE STAT: The 2000 National Championship MSU team played 5 games that season against teams that made the Final Four and went 5-0?", "answer": "Not really a big reveal about Wisconsin. Anyone that knows anything about that championship season would have that near or at the top of things to remember."}, {"id": 10, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that INSANE STAT: The 2000 National Championship MSU team played 5 games that season against teams that made the Final Four and went 5-0?", "answer": "? how is it twisted ? it\u2019s a literal fact\n\n\nEDIT: It was actually 6 wins. They played the other final four team, UNC, during the regular season and won."}, {"id": 11, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that INSANE STAT: The 2000 National Championship MSU team played 5 games that season against teams that made the Final Four and went 5-0?", "answer": "that\u2019s insane. wow. Thanks for sharing"}, {"id": 12, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Decisions for Fall 2024 Transfer?", "answer": "I put mine in on December 8th and was accepted on February 22nd"}, {"id": 13, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Decisions for Fall 2024 Transfer?", "answer": "Yes. I got accepted as a CS major 2 weeks ago. I applied on the 7th of January. Applied as a transfer though not as a first year"}, {"id": 14, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Decisions for Fall 2024 Transfer?", "answer": "It might take the College of Engineering some time to review it."}, {"id": 15, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Decisions for Fall 2024 Transfer?", "answer": "What is ur major?"}, {"id": 16, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Decisions for Fall 2024 Transfer?", "answer": "Cong!"}, {"id": 17, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Decisions for Fall 2024 Transfer?", "answer": "My first two choices were engineering but they ended up putting me with my fall back, political science, because I was missing a few required classes."}, {"id": 18, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "Even with the scholarship, studying in the US is crazy expensive. Have you considered studying in Europe?"}, {"id": 19, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "As someone who has lived in Minneapolis, go green all the way. umn is such a bore and honestly people were curb stomping people right off campus for funsies last year. Also more people have a more positive view of msu than umn"}, {"id": 20, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "Definitely do it - I'm on the board of the data science program.  You won't regret it."}, {"id": 21, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "I think you should look into the school rankings. The difference in COA is not too large compared to your willingness to pay. Choose the school that offers you more flexibility in changing career path/coursework etc. Opportunities are scarce for internationals, so be practical."}, {"id": 22, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "Do it. I am international and paying 40K. Lots of internationals are paying 65K."}, {"id": 23, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "Go for it if aid is not a problem"}, {"id": 24, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "I\u2019m CDS major and love it! MSU has a very exciting CMSE department that emphasizes pedagogy over the hardcore weeder lecture style of traditional CSE classes"}, {"id": 25, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "[deleted]"}, {"id": 26, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "My parents can afford up to 35k so i dont have much issues with financial aspect. I just want to know the quality of education and the environment here"}, {"id": 27, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "Have your students had luck getting roles with just the bachelors? I\u2019m curious because my company has now made a masters a requirement"}, {"id": 28, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "Im dont know if difficulty is rigorous enough for me bc ive heard someone said msu program is ez. What do you think?"}, {"id": 29, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "How can they afford that much :0. I'd go to Purdue if i can pay 40k"}, {"id": 30, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "Sure! Im leaning toward it!"}, {"id": 31, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "Sorry dude, I'm vietnamese"}, {"id": 32, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "A year or a semester"}, {"id": 33, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "Yeah man, surprised you know that since we try to keep it a secret. Our data science program is just learning how to count with goldfish and cheese itz. If you think you're too smart for that I'd probably just go elsewhere"}, {"id": 34, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "L purdue"}, {"id": 35, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "A year"}, {"id": 36, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Should I Go Green! ??", "answer": "Purdue is not that hard"}, {"id": 37, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Advertising & marketing grads/alumni. Where do you work now??", "answer": "1. Advertising management \n2. Had a job lined up at an ad agency in Detroit before graduation. \n3. Working in client side advertising at a major teleco. \n4. Pay & total comp is much better client side than agency side, can\u2019t complain."}, {"id": 38, "question": "How is Reddit responding to the recent news that Need a 3rd roomie for van hoosen?", "answer": "I\u2019m interested! I dmed you :)"}]}